muziic.com 2013-11-26

# Muziic - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Muziic stores information that we collect through cookies, log files, and clear gifs to create a "profile" of your preferences. This statistical information may be used to help Muziic provide tailored services and to improve the content of the site for you.

Giving us your personal data on this site is completely optional and will require you to setup an account with a password and an email address. You may also submit additional personal information (including data on your profile and on message boards). Please remember that any information you submit becomes public information that can be viewed by others.

The Publish Playback feature allows users who are logged into their Muziic accounts to share playlist data information from the Muziic Player. By default, the Publish Playback feature is enabled for users who have logged into the Muziic Player. Users may opt out of this feature by disabling Publish Playback in the Muziic Player settings menu. With Muziic Web Player, Publish Playback is always on, however, users may logout to avoid attributing plays to their account.

We may use the email address provided by you to contact you from time to time about offers, or other related services. We will NOT share your personally identifiable information (email address, first or last name, etc.) with ANY third-party or partner unless you explicitly request us to do so.

The Muziic service may display links to third party sites. We advise you to check their terms of use and privacy policies before submitting your personal information to them.

Google, a third party vendor, may use cookies to serve advertisements on the Muziic site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>
